trueos.org 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy - TrueOS

At iXsystems, we value user privacy and are committed to disclosing how information is collected and used. This Privacy Policy outlines how iXsystems collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users of our website, products, and services (“Products”).

### Personal Information

We may collect and store personally identifying information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our website, register on the website, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities on this website, services, features or resources we make available on our website or through the use of the Products. Users may be prompted to enter information, including, name, email address, company name, and other information needed to process your requests. Users may, however, visit our website anonymously and not provide personal identifying information. We will collect personal identifying information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us and give us consent.

### Non-personal Information

To ensure necessary and optimal performance of the Products, we may collect non-personal identification information from you when you interact with our website(s) and/or Products. Non-personal information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about means of connection to our website, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Cookies

trueos.org may use “cookies” to enhance your experience. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you, including how you interact with our Products. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert when a website attempts to use a cookie. If you do so, note that some pieces of our website may not function as well.

### How We Use Your Information

iXsystems may collect and use your personal and non-personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To run and operate trueos.org_ – We may need your information to display content on the website correctly.
  * _To improve customer service_ – Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _To personalize your experience_ – We may use aggregated information to understand how our users interact with our website.
  * _To make improvements to our website –_ We may use feedback you give to improve our Products..
  * _To send occasional emails_ – If you sign up for our email list you can easily unsubscribe by clicking “unsubscribe” at the bottom of any email you receive from iXsystems.

### How We Protect Personal Information

iXsystems uses appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices, as well as additional security measures and procedures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our website.

### Sharing Personal Information

iXsystems does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers for purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### Affiliate Programs

iXsystems is part of the Amazon Associates partner program and may monetize links to Amazon by adding a referral tag to amazon.com addresses. This allows us to earn a modest commision when referring others to amazon.com.

### Electronic Newsletters

iXsystems uses third party service providers to help us operate our business and websites. Third party services may also administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys that you have voluntarily signed up to receive. We may share your information with these third parties for the limited purposes described in this Privacy Policy provided that you have given us your permission by submitting an email sign-up form.

### Third Party Websites

You may find content on trueos.org that links to websites operated by our affiliates, Open Source partner projects, or services of other partners. We do not control the content or links that appear on these websites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites that link to our website. In addition, these websites, including their content and links, may be constantly changing and these sites operate under different privacy policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our website, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. iXsystems collects information through third party analytics providers that allows us to analyze trends, demographics, and various statistics about your interaction with our website. Any analytics data collected does not contain personal identifiable information.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

iXsystems may update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage users to frequently check our Privacy Policy page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of any modifications.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this website, you are agreeing to our terms of use and Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this policy, you must not use [www.trueos.org](http://www.trueos.org/). Continued use of our website following the posting of changes to this policy will be understood as your acceptance of any changes.

### GDPR Compliance

iXsystems is committed to GDPR compliance and offers this Privacy Policy as a means to demonstrate how data may be used when visiting this website and using our Products. iXsystems does not collect personal identifying information unless the user has taken an intentional action to fill out a form and request contact. If you are in the European Union, you may request that identifying information that you have submitted be removed from our database by [contacting us](mailto:legal@ixsystems.com). Learn more about the GDPR by visiting the [official website](https://www.eugdpr.org/).

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of how we operate this website, or your dealings with this website, please [contact us](mailto:legal@ixsystems.com).

This document was last updated on May 3rd, 2018.
